// deckData.js
const deckData = [
  {
    deckName: "Deck 1",
    deckDescription: "1 term",
    userName: "Creator 1",
    createDate: "10/10/2022",
    cards: [
      { cardFront: "Dolor sit amet", cardBack: "Consectetur adipiscing elit" },
      {
        cardFront: "Ut enim ad minim veniam",
        cardBack: "Sed do eiusmod tempor",
      },
      { cardFront: "Dolor sit amet", cardBack: "Lorem ipsum" },
      { cardFront: "Sed do eiusmod tempor", cardBack: "Dolor sit amet" },
      {
        cardFront: "Consectetur adipiscing elit",
        cardBack: "Ut enim ad minim veniam",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    deckName: "Deck 2",
    deckDescription: "2 terms",
    userName: "Creator 2",
    createDate: "11/10/2022",
    cards: [
      { cardFront: "Dolor sit amet", cardBack: "Consectetur adipiscing elit" },
      {
        cardFront: "Ut enim ad minim veniam",
        cardBack: "Sed do eiusmod tempor",
      },
      { cardFront: "Dolor sit amet", cardBack: "Lorem ipsum" },
      { cardFront: "Sed do eiusmod tempor", cardBack: "Dolor sit amet" },
      {
        cardFront: "Consectetur adipiscing elit",
        cardBack: "Ut enim ad minim veniam",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    deckName: "Deck 3",
    deckDescription: "3 terms",
    userName: "Creator 3",
    createDate: "12/10/2022",
    cards: [
      { cardFront: "Dolor sit amet", cardBack: "Consectetur adipiscing elit" },
      {
        cardFront: "Ut enim ad minim veniam",
        cardBack: "Sed do eiusmod tempor",
      },
      { cardFront: "Dolor sit amet", cardBack: "Lorem ipsum" },
      { cardFront: "Sed do eiusmod tempor", cardBack: "Dolor sit amet" },
      {
        cardFront: "Consectetur adipiscing elit",
        cardBack: "Ut enim ad minim veniam",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    deckName: "Deck 4",
    deckDescription: "3 terms",
    userName: "Creator 3",
    createDate: "12/10/2022",
    cards: [
      { cardFront: "Dolor sit amet", cardBack: "Consectetur adipiscing elit" },
      {
        cardFront: "Ut enim ad minim veniam",
        cardBack: "Sed do eiusmod tempor",
      },
      { cardFront: "Dolor sit amet", cardBack: "Lorem ipsum" },
      { cardFront: "Sed do eiusmod tempor", cardBack: "Dolor sit amet" },
      {
        cardFront: "Consectetur adipiscing elit",
        cardBack: "Ut enim ad minim veniam",
      },
    ],
  },
  {
    deckName: "Deck 5",
    deckDescription: "3 terms",
    userName: "Creator 3",
    createDate: "12/10/2022",
    cards: [
      { cardFront: "Dolor sit amet", cardBack: "Consectetur adipiscing elit" },
      {
        cardFront: "Ut enim ad minim veniam",
        cardBack: "Sed do eiusmod tempor",
      },
      { cardFront: "Dolor sit amet", cardBack: "Lorem ipsum" },
      { cardFront: "Sed do eiusmod tempor", cardBack: "Dolor sit amet" },
      {
        cardFront: "Consectetur adipiscing elit",
        cardBack: "Ut enim ad minim veniam",
      },
    ],
  },
  // Add more decks as needed
];

export default deckData;
